{
    "subject": "resource/The_Clock_(1945_film)",
    "predicate": "property/country",
    "object": "United States",
    "human_readable": "The Clock (1945 film) was produced in the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9524025917053223,
            "question": "Where was 'The Clock' (1945 film) produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8528842926025391,
            "question": "What country was responsible for producing 'The Clock' (1945 film)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8459619879722595,
            "question": "What type of film is 'The Clock' (1945)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7813761830329895,
            "question": "What is the genre of 'The Clock' (1945 film)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7161043882369995,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'The Clock' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6806880235671997,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the setting of 'The Clock' (1945 film)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6294887065887451,
            "question": "Are there any interesting facts about the making of 'The Clock' (1945)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5144864320755005,
            "question": "Were there any notable actors in 'The Clock' (1945)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42888131737709045,
            "question": "Is 'The Clock' a Hollywood production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3459640443325043,
            "question": "Is 'The Clock' a popular or well-known film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Clock (1945 film) was produced in the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7092_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Clock' a Hollywood production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7092_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable actors in 'The Clock' (1945)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7092_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any interesting facts about the making of 'The Clock' (1945)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7092_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7092_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your question:\n\n{'output': 'yes'} \n\nThis is because the documents mention that \"The Clock\" is a 1945 American romance film directed by Vincente Minnelli, indicating that it was produced in the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents supports that \"The Clock\" is a 1945 American romance film, which implies it was indeed produced in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}